MODHUMITA PAIK

Business Development Executive

An experienced business development executive with a proven track record of driving revenue growth and expanding market share for companies across various industries. With 5.2 years of experience in business development, sales, counseling and marketing, I have a deep understanding of the sales process and have developed a keen ability to identify and pursue new business opportunities.

Work History

2022-08 -Current

Pre Sales / Sales Executive ((B2B & B2C)

LIVSPACE HOME INTERIOR, Bengaluru

- Identify new business opportunities through research, networking, and other means
- Develop relationships with potential clients and maintain ongoing communication Negotiate and close deals to drive revenue growth
- Experience with CRM systems and sales forecasting tools
- Manage the sales process from qualifying lead to closing deals, and ensure customer satisfaction throughout
- Develop and maintain a strong pipeline of potential clients and opportunities and Scheduled meeting between designers and clients
- Follow up with potential customers in a timely manner if necessary
- Meet personal/team qualitative and quantitative targets
- Follow-up with internal stakeholders to ensure that appropriate action has been taken on customer requests and complaints.

2021-04 -2022-07

Business Development Executive (B2B & B2C)

RICE EDUCATION, Kolkata

 Handle incoming queries and make outgoing calls to prospects and Understand students need



Contact

Address

Madhu Niwas, 16/1 Coconut Garden St, Madiwala, BTM 1st Stage, Bengaluru, India 560068

Phone

9073432802

E-mail

modhumitapaik91@gmail.c

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/modhumita-paik-2008561

www

https://bold.pro /my/modhumitapaik-230723015630/495

Skills

Business development and planning

Lead Generation

and give them right path

- Counseling Students and parents about our courses and competition exams landscape.
- Provide career counseling and guidance to prospects students Virtually and face to face
- Handle student's complaints and issues students' unhappiness by immediately acknowledging the issue
- Assist school administrators and educators with planning and carrying out Our programs and events. Relationship Building and Negotiation with Vendors/ Partners
- Achieve monthly revenue targets from upselling and referrals from current students.
- Make entries in to CRM, Lead Management
 System and another database as required

2019-02 - Academic Counselor

2021-03 MAY

MAYA ACADEMY OF ADVANCE CINEMATICS, Kolkata

- Outbound calls & follow up calls on a daily basis with prospective students & their parents.
- Fix appointments and conduct demo sessions on a daily basis with prospective students & their parents.
- Handle Objections and Price Negotiation to generate Sales Revenue.
- Maintain MIS of calling students.
- Provide career counseling and guidance to prospects students through phone calls, Zoom and face to face.
- Collaborated with school faculty to define and prioritize departmental strategies and direction.
- Provided support and guidance to students experiencing academic and personal troubles.

2018-01 - ASSISTANT TEACHER

2019-01

BANGA BANDHU MODEL SCHOOL, Kolkata

- Supported student physical, mental, and social development using classroom games and activities.
- Kept students on-task with proactive behavior modification and positive reinforcement strategies.
- Completed daily reports, meal count sheets, and

Cold Calling

Operations

Sales forecasting

CRM (Salesforce, Ozontel, Ameeyo)

Product and service sales

Time management

B2B sales

Presales Strategy Design

Goals and performance

Sales expertise

Languages

Hindi

•••••
Advanced

English

•••••
Advanced

Bengali

•••••
Advanced

Personal Information

Father Name : Paritosh
 Paik

• DOB: 2nd June, 1992

• Category: SC

Marital Status :
 Unmarried

• Sex: Female

Education

2010-06 - 2014-07

attendance logs.

- Oversaw students in classroom and common areas to monitor, enforce rules, and support lead teacher.
- Assisted in planning and development of teaching materials, workbooks and class projects.

Certifications

2015-02 Diploma in Information Technology - [Youth

Computer Centr] - MS WORD , MS EXCEL ,FOXPRO 6 ,POWERPOINT ,MS ACCESSV, ISUAL BASIC, INTERNET & EMAIL ADVANCE EXCEL (Google Sheet , Pivot

Table , V- Lookup , H- Look Up)

2023-06 Post Graduate Program in Digital Marketing [Purdue

University - Pursuing]

DECLARATION

I, hereby solemnly declare that all the information made above are true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Bachelor of Arts: Geography (Honours)

Calcutta University -Kolkata

2008-04 - 2010-05

HIGHER SECONDARY: Arts

WBCHSE - Kolkata

2002-02 - 2008-05

SECONDARY: Arts

WBBSE - Kolkata

Hobbies

- Travelling
- Reading non fiction books
- Listening Songs
- Decorating Home